<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Feed Name</title>
  <link href="http://domain/"/>
  <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://domain/atom.xml"/>
  <updated>5/06/2012 8:49:06 PM</updated>
  <id>http://domain/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Author</name>
    <email>Email</email>
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <id>http://domain//2012/06/05/ithinkifinallygetit.html</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://domain//2012/06/05/ithinkifinallygetit.html"/>
    <title>I think I finally get it.</title>
    <updated>5/06/2012 12:00:00 AM</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Author</name>
      <uri>http://domain/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html"><h2>I think I finally get it.</h2>
<p>I started using Windows 8 with the first release of the Developer Preview. I've installed each version since, yet by and large, the OS has thoroughly unimpressed me. I found it very cumbersome to use with a mouse and keyboard. I couldn't really see what Microsoft was aiming for.</p>
<p>But today, I think I have started to understand.</p>
<p>A heap of new hardware was announced at Computex today. The one item that really took my interest was the ASUS Transformer Book.</p>
<p>It's a notebook, running the full version of Windows 8 (none of this Windows RT stuff!), but it can detach the screen and work as a full tablet. It can be configured with an Ivy Bridge i7 CPU, with a reasonable 4GB max of RAM (although 8GB would have been much better for me), and of course SSD, etc.</p>
<p>For the very first time, I can see a use of Windows 8 in my life. If this was matched with a good digitizer (possible?) and the possibility of multiple external monitors (unlikely, but hopeful), this may very well be a great setup for both home and work.</p>
<p>I am, for the first time, actually starting to take an interest in Windows 8.</p>
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://domain//2012/06/05/myfirstpost.html</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://domain//2012/06/05/myfirstpost.html"/>
    <title>My First Post</title>
    <updated>5/06/2012 12:00:00 AM</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Author</name>
      <uri>http://domain/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html"><h2>Hello world...</h2>
<p>This is my first post on the site!</p>
</content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>